John Hewitt

E-mail or Github preferred: jhnh198@gmail.com

Github: https://github.com/jhnh198

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/john-h-3361297a/

Phone Number provided on request

Summary: Seeking web developer role using React/Node but open to any other framework. Education in Java and completed a Bachelor of Science in Computer Science. 2 years tech support experience. Left tech in 2019 and in 2022 re-joined the IT field.

Current Role:

Trimble Transportation: Technical Support Representative(Jan 2022 - present)

- Provide level 1 support Electronic Logging Device(ELD) software for business customers in the US and Canada.
- Troubleshoot hardware and software(android and in-house apps)
- Salesforce Lightning CRM for casing
- Recommended implementing mock calls to train agents supporting Trimble's latest ELD software, Instinct, while we are on a pilot program that includes supporting a major US carrier.

Relevant Experience:

Randstad: Help Desk Analyst (Aug 2017 - March 2019)

- Assist users in a fast-paced enterprise environment. 40+ calls per day
- Support Windows, mainframe applications and mobile
- Typical calls were password resets, web and desktop application issues including freezing, troubleshooting error messages and assisting with permission issues.
- ServiceNow ticketing software
- Troubleshooting and diagnosing issues from information gathering

US Foods: Web Application Development Intern (May 2015 - Jan 2016)

- Developed Front-End for Ecommerce and Business Applications using Oracle ADF
- Worked with JIRA Project Management tools
- Explored deployment of VDI for developer teams with senior leadership to provide research for cost and viability.

Amazon Warehouse, Uber during 2019-2022

Technologies: Javascript, React, Node, PostgreSQL, Java, Python

Education:

Northeastern Illinois University, Chicago IL

Graduated Dec 2016

- Bachelor's of Science in Computer Science. 3.2 GPA
- Vice President: NEIU Computer Science Society